Thank you for watching!
Thanks again for all your hard work!
Hallo! This time we have with us Rika Shimakura from BEYOOOOONDS Subway and
BEYOOOOONDS, Minami Okamura from Ameagari Kawahama!
We will be presenting this time with these two, so please stay with us until the end.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
We are pleased to announce that we will be leaving the Sendai concert on February 25th.
Hello! Project 2023 Winter 2 ofus tour has ended with the performance in Sendai on February 25.
Thank you very much for your support.
Thank you very much.
This time you had a 2-man show with Juice- Juice, which was a new experiment for you, wasn't it? What about this tour?
Juice-Juice's songs are very mature and have a calm atmosphere, while BEYOOOOONDS's songs are bright and full of energy, which is a completely different group.
I thought it was an interesting concert to see how they combined their different atmospheres.
They covered each other's songs.
BEYOOOOONDS covered Juice Juice's "Tell Me You Love Me.
Miho has never sung such a mature song before, so I was very nervous.
I was very nervous, but it was an interesting scientific reaction and I really enjoyed the tour.
The spring concert tour will start on March 18.
BEYOOOOONDS's title is "BEYOOOOONDS Concert Tour Neo Beyo."
The first day of BEYOOOOONDS's tour will be on the 19th.
The first day of BEYOOOOONDS's tour will be on the 19th, and since it is called "Neo," I think it will be a tour where I can show you a new BEYOOOOONDS.
Please look forward to it.
And on April 12, BEYOOOOONDS will release her new single, which will be her first single in about a year and a month.
Yay!
This time, it is a double A-side single, "Seek yo, Fateful Traveler" and "Yume wo naki nakuenai yozora ni" (In the night sky where you can't even draw a dream).
We performed "Seek yo, Fated Traveler" for the first time at the Hello!
How did you like it? How did you feel when you performed it?
Project concert in winter.
I was really nervous.
The reaction of the audience was pretty good, even though it was the first time they had heard the song.
That's right. There was a lot of clapping in the music, so the response was great, and it was a lot of fun.
The response was wonderful, and it was a lot of fun.
Please look forward to the new single to be released on April 12!
Let's start with this video.
Please enjoy!
Thanks for your hard work.
I had it with natto, the sticky stuff.
I'll get the rice with you, egg and all.
I'll eat it as it is. The sticky rice is a red string.
It's a red string, therefore.
The battle begins at 7:00 a.m.
You're One Hot Boy at the Katakura
I always end up baking, my love
Sometimes I'm selfish
Don't you think you should at least try?
The weather's fine, and it's Takidate forty-five
Shaycee, you're my favorite
Under one roof
Rice and wheat
We used to be friends
Let's not fight
Never Never No
Even if we're always by each other's side
There are some things you just don't know
I'm tired of doubting
I don't know what I'll do tomorrow
Never Never No
Everything about you is sweet chuus
Please subscribe to our channel!
Oh, why was I born a rice girl?
And why are you a bread person?
Who decided rice for natto and butter for bread?
How about this? Bread and rice for breakfast?
No, I don't care if it's Nana.
Because I want to eat with you every day.
A Tale of Two Unforgivable Acts
Two acts that can mix
For the sake of love, let's take each other's hands
I put the rice timer on
Never Never No
If You're Always By My Side
Can We Understand Each Other
If it's your favorite place, of course
No matter what it is, everywhere it's Tomorrow
Never Never No
I'll eat with you
I want to eat it with natto.
Never Never No
Let's put it on a piece of crispy toast
on a piece of fluffy toast.
Never, never, never
It's a red string, I dreamed it
Never Ever I'll never leave you
Never Ever
Never Ever Hold me tight
Having fun? Watch the rest of the show.
Rika Shimakura of BEYOOOOONDS Subway and
BEYOOOOONDS Rainy Morikawa Umi no Okamura Minami presents Halo! Stay!
From here, we'd like to talk a little bit about each other.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm going to ask you some questions, so don't think too much and answer them quickly.
March is graduation season
What do you want to graduate now?
IndoorsyIndoorsy
BEYOOOOONDS 4th single to be released on April 12
If you had to give this single a catchphrase, what would it be?
Towards the future.
I like it.
What is the highlight of this single?
Shiori Nishida's whistle voice in "Seek Me, Destiny's Traveler".
I know what you mean.
What movies have you seen recently that you would recommend?
Pretty Princess
Hello! Project celebrates its 25th anniversary this year
Is there a costume you would like to try on at least once?
Gakuran worn by Shin Maeda, the boy with glasses.
Oh!
Yes!
Thank you very much.
Now I'd like to ask you a few questions about some of the things I'm interested in.
What do you want to graduate from, indoor school?
Yes, I'm an indoor person.
I'm the type of person who stays at home on my days off.
I'm just graduating from high school.
That's right.
I would like to take this opportunity to go to many places
I'm going to travel a lot and have a lot of experiences
to be a wonderful adult who can experience many things.
That's great.
I want to graduate from being an indoor person
I want to experience all kinds of things.
That's nice.
Okay, one more thing.
An outfit I'd like to try on.
Yes.
The boy with glasses.
Yes, Shin Maeda always plays the role of a boy with glasses.
I think you always wear a school uniform as a boy with glasses.
I've never dressed up as a man before, so I can't imagine what it's like.
I can't imagine it.
I've never worn Gakuran either.
Once... as an experience.
Well, it might be interesting.
I thought it would be fun.
I'd like to try it on.
I had a bit of a crush on you.
Something like that.
Thank you very much.
We'll take questions from Rika Shimakura after the VTR.
Hello! Ste.
Tsubaki Factory No Mistake, No Crying Now on sale
Tsubaki Factory Skip skip skip skip Now on sale
Hitori deyorenaitai, furikake mitsumo Tsubaki Factory Kimi to boku no kizuna Featuring Kiki Now on sale
Our turn, all on Go, the show is still here, the whole earth is going to the stage
Hallo! Stage!
Next, I'd like to ask Rika Shimakura a question.
Please do.
It's been a month and a half since all the members started Instagram. What has changed since you started SNS?
I started taking a lot of pictures.
It's been almost 5 years since you joined us as trainees. How would you describe this period in one word?
Love
What are you working on now to improve yourself?
Brushing my teeth.
I'm going to ask you the same question again, but what's the funniest movie you've seen recently?
A movie called "The Musician Who Loved Movies" by Kone Mori was interesting.
Project 25 years of songs, which is your favorite song that reminds you of Showa era?
Country Musume。 Project, Kondo-san and Fujimoto-san's song "Shining Aishiki Anata".
Thank you very much.
Okay, I'd like to talk about a few things that have been on my mind.
You joined as a trainee and have been with us ever since.
It's amazing that you joined Nuance from a trainee group, isn't it?
I think it's wonderful that you are all from different ages and different regions, and that you have spent all your time together as trainees, getting along well with each other.
I look forward to working with you.
The other one is a song by Hello! Project with a Showa-esque feel.
Shining Aishiki You
The tempo of this song is a bit slow.
And the lyrics are very Showa-esque.
It's true.
The guy in the lyrics is a bit of a jerk
I thought it was a little bit like that
I really like this song.
I've never thought of it as a Showa song.
I'd like to listen to it from that point of view.
Hallo! Stay tuned for more after this!
I'm Sei Fukumura from Morning Musume。 I'm Sei Fukumura from Morning Musume' 23.
I'll be cooking again this week.
What are you going to cook?
Grilled pork loin!
Wow, it looks delicious!
Sprinkle a little rub on it.
I've been helping you since I was a little girl.
So I'm used to it.
I don't like to boil it, so I'm just going to rinse it.
It's a little big as it is.
Bigger.
Let's go with this size.
Yes.
Put them in this.
Potatoes have a certain amount of water in them.
So it's fine like this.
But don't tie them together.
It's better to microwave them in a separated state.
If they're stuck together, they won't burn as well.
I see.I see.
I'll give you about two minutes.
I'll check on it and if it's not in the microwave, I'll add some more.
Okay, put it in the microwave.
(In the home, 500 or 600 watts for 2 minutes.)
Sprinkle some salt on the asparagus.
Roll them around.
If the water content of the asparagus is a little low
Wet the paper.
Microwaving adds power to the moisture.
I don't think it's in there yet.
So, take it over here once.
Let's heat it up.
Once it's hot...
It becomes transparent.
But the color is different here in the middle.
If you poke and prod it...
It's hard.
Let's see for a minute.
About 10 minutes.
Look at this
That's a lot of water.
It's like it was just a pinch, and now it's just...
Looks delicious.
Shall I cut a slit in this side?
Here you go.
And the potatoes.
It's all right now.
Smells good.
Then we put them in the box.
Put them in.
It's like a grill pan.
We're going to grill this, this, this, and the asparagus.
Potatoes and marshmallows are sautéed in the pan.
Sauté them and brown them nicely.
I split the asparagus.
Be careful with the asparagus.
It's hot
Once in the hot water and popped in the water
Isn't the color so beautiful?
When it cools down, the color stays bright.
and it stays bright.
Baked!
This one is cooked, so the main thing is just to get the color right.
Mushrooms are raw, so you want to make sure they're cooked through.
They are pretty spongy.
I want them to absorb the oil just right.
When you cook them when they are crispy, you can get the right color.
I use a tablespoon of olive oil.
This side is hard to color because it rolls around, so you want to make sure the color is on this side.
Yes, let it absorb this oil.
Just a little bit on this side.
Yes, it's not so good.
If the potatoes have a little moisture on them, they will pop even more.
So, do it like this.
Yes, sir.
Yes, yes, yes.
There's almost no more oil.
I think it's time to turn it over. But let's turn it over.
Wow, it looks so good, smells so good...
If it's about to burn, I'll let it go a little.
I'll let it go a little bit.
There's not enough oil for the potatoes, so I'll turn down the heat.
I'm going to lower the heat.
The heat is high at first, but when the color comes to this level, the oil is hot.
The oil temperature is high, so it's important to get this color.
Looks delicious.
Yes, it looks delicious.
Sprinkle a little salt on it.
It's all right now.
Potatoes, too.
Salt too?
Yes, just a little.
Straight lines don't look good.
At an angle.
To make it diagonal...
To make it diagonal, you have to put it on the side like this.
Or you can put it straight at an angle.
Is this okay here?
Oh, not yet.
Not yet?
Not at all. You have to do it until the smoke comes out.
It doesn't have any color now.
If you put a little olive oil on the surface...
The color will come out.
Shall we leave it?
Let's put it on.
Yes, at an angle.
In one stroke.
Yes, in one stroke.
But once you put it down, you can't move it.
You can't move it.
How's the angle?
Uh, it's okay.
It's the same angle now.
Okay.
Now, from the top, squeeze it like this.And then, from the top, squeeze it like this
Yes.
Yes, sir.
I'm starting to feel a little sorry for him.
Without this pressure, the lines don't come out cleanly, so they get cut off in the middle.
In professional work, you have to press down on it.
Do you press down so hard?
Or when you go for a stone or something...
Maybe I'm still a little naive.
But it's okay.
I'm gentle.
I'm pretty aggressive.
I'll take a look.
You're going to put it in?
Not quite.
Wow, that's what it feels like.
Wow!
If it's smoking, it means that the moisture is gone.
Wow, these eggplants are getting burnt!
I've already done this eggplant over here.
I've been very thorough.
I'm sure it's already attached.
Yes, but that's the right answer.
I think it's attached, but it's a little hard here... on the buttocks.
I'll wait a little longer.
It's burnt.
It's perfect.
You can cook it a little longer than I thought.
I'm sure it'll change.
I could smell the burnt smell... but it's just a little bit.
You said something nice earlier about it being hard here.
If it's hard to the touch, it's not cooked yet.
If it's a little squishy, it's a little squishy.
It's a little squishy.
Are you okay? Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
I just want to say good night.
Good job.
Ready?
How is it?
Wow, it's absolutely delicious.
Mmm! Mmm!
Mmm!
I can't wait to see it finished.
Yes, I am.
So, on the subject of cooking...
Do you want to cook?
Cooking? Sometimes.
I cook quite a bit.
Really? You must work pretty hard.
I do my best. I used to make it myself.
What do you cook?
Lately, I've been eating hot pot every day.
Cooking, I mean.
It's cooking.
It's fine cooking.
How about you, Rika?
I'm also working very hard.
Nabe (hot pot).
It's delicious, isn't it? You can eat it every day.
It's cold, isn't it?
What kind of nabe are you making?
Yose-nabe? I like nabe with regular dashi broth.
I see.
What about you, Rika?
I really like soy milk nabe.
I also like kimchi nabe. I often make it.
Wow. That's so nice.
One-pot dish together.
Here they come.
I want to eat it.
There are girls who like it, right, BEYOOOOONDS?
Let's go together.
Yes, I will.
Hallo! Stay!
Next is the presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart.
Project, there are many beautiful lyrical phrases in their songs.
Project, but this time we have chosen one from each of them.
I am Juice-Juice.
I chose a small dream in a small town in Juice-Juice's song "Baby Love".
I really like the lyric, "Your dream is so big that my heart trembled.
It resonates so much.
I can imagine so many things from this one phrase.
I can imagine my classmates talking about their dreams for the future.
I love the lyrics because I can imagine my classmates talking about their dreams for the future and how they will spread to the rest of their lives.
I love it.
I, Okamura, was listening to a song by ℃-ute called "La la la la la," which is a song about happiness.
I wanted to listen to a spring-like song since it will soon be spring, and this was the first song I had heard in a while.
I hadn't heard this song in a while.
In the A melody of the second verse, the song says that girls will always be girls, and that they are always interested in cute accessories.
Cute.
It's cute, isn't it? It's the kind of lyric that just makes you swoon.
I think the lyrics sound like they are sung by a girl who wants to grow up a bit, but who is too grown up and likes cute things forever.
I thought the lyrics were even cuter if I joined hands and feet with the singer.
It's a lyric I've heard recently.
It's really good. I heard them too.
Now please watch the VTR. Please watch the VTR.
The lyrics that touched my heart presentation. In this corner, we will present the lyrics of Hello!
Project's songs, and talk about the charm of the lyrics.
Project's songs and talk about the charm of the lyrics. Project songs and talk about their charms.I hope that you, the viewers of Halo! I hope you, the readers of Halo!
This time, I, Sakura Ishiyama, will make the presentation.
Here it is.
Tetteren!
If you have fulfilled one dream, shift to the next one. If you have time to dwell on memories, polish your skills and eat delicious food!
This song is called "Keep On Ascending" by JuiceJuice.
When I was a trainee at Halo Pro, I performed "Keep On Ascending" in a diagnostic test.
In the test, we only sang the first number.
But after I joined JuiceJuice, I read the lyrics again.
I reread the lyrics again.
In the second verse, the lyrics say that if you have fulfilled one dream, you can shift to the next dream, and so on.
It's very selfish, but I thought it was the perfect lyric for me right now.
I really like eating delicious food, so I thought this phrase was perfect for me.
I love eating delicious food, so I chose this phrase because I thought it was perfect for me.
I think it's one of the songs that inspires me, and I think JuiceJuice is a very energetic song.
It is quite rare for JuiceJuice to have a very cheerful song.
Most of them are a bit mature, slow, or mid-tempo.
This song is a very bright song, and it gets a lot of people excited at live performances.
I hope to bring this brightness and positive feeling to the audience.
If I have achieved one dream, my other dream is to debut as a trainee.
The next dream is to see what I will do after my debut.
The lyrics are very supportive, and I like them very much.
The chorus of the song also has a very encouraging lyric about trying over and over again.
The chorus also has lyrics that really cheer you up.
Please listen to the song if you want to be cheered up.
I hope you will be encouraged and keep going forward.
Please look forward to the next installment!
Hallo! STE!
BEYOOOOONDS with Rika Shimakura of Subway
BEYOOOOONDS, Minami Okamura of Morikawa Umi in the Rain, and Rika Shimakura of BEYOOOOONDS Subway will be joining us on Halo! Stay!
As I mentioned in the opening, BEYOOOOONDS will be performing on April 12 for the first time in about a year and a month.
BEYOOOOONDS will release their 4th single on April 12, after a year and a month.
Seek Me, Fate's Traveler Mountain
In the night sky where you can't even draw a dream
will be released!
Yay!
Yes, "Seek yo Fate no Tabibito Yama" is the one!
As the name "Tabijinzan" suggests, it is a combination of "Tabijinzan", which appears in mathematics
and life, traveler.
It is a song that encourages us to work hard for the future.
Yes, and in the night sky where I can't even draw a dream
It is a very grand song arranged by a brass band.
The lyrics are positive and bright, and they really resonate with the heart.
I think it's a very beautiful song.
Yes, we have grown up.
I am sure you will be able to see how we have grown.
Yes, we will also be releasing video works for three consecutive months.
We are also releasing a new video on February 1, 2012.
Beyond's 1st concert tour "Mouicho! Be Happy!
This is the Blu-ray of the 1st concert tour in spring.
This is the encore performance of the 1st concert tour in spring.
I think you can see the culmination of the 1st concert tour on this Blu-ray.
And it will be released next week on March 8.
I hope you will also check out the Blu-ray of "Theatre Girls Club Saillou Palace" which will be released next week on March 8.
Marie Antoinette, played by Yuha Yamazaki, comes to the present day by chance and tries her best as an idol.
I hope you will check it out.
BEYOOOOONDS's 2nd concert tour will be released on April 12, the same day as the release of the single.
This Blu-ray release will be released on April 12, the same day as the release of the single, and will include many songs from the second album, so please check it out.
Please check it out and have a great time with BEYOOOOONDS this spring, not only at her live concerts but also through her singles and Blu-ray releases.
It will make you smile.
It will bring tears to your eyes.
You will have fun
It's frustrating at times
I have a family
You have me.
You have that little boy.
You've got the earth
Here we go.
It's a wonder party
Don't be shy
Time to be free
Yeah! Break out!
Don't be shy, don't be shy
It's you who decides if you're happy
It's up to you
Hello! You were born with a meaning
I was born for a reason.
I'm not mad at you anymore, my hands are the highest
I'm losing to the grown-ups and I'm flapping my wings
I love any weapon you can give me
Subtitle: Kiyo Mouse
Hello, since I was born
I'm sure there must be a meaning to it by now
I won't get mad if I win
Even if I fall down, I'll still be the best in the race
Though I'll spread my wings before I grow up
Hey!
I love you no matter what
Uh Uh Uh Uh Yeah!
I'm always on your side.
I'll always be on your side. Good luck!
Beyonds Rika Shimakura of Subway and
Beyonds Rainy Morikawa Umi no Okamura Minami presents Halo! Stay!
It's time to say goodbye.
Here is an announcement.
On April 12, we will be releasing a new single, Seek Me, Fate's Traveler!
Yume wo nakurenai yozora ni mune, will be released on April 12.
And Beyonds second concert tour
Blue Rain in Autumn will also be released.
And next week, on March 8, Blue Rain of Theater Girl's Club Beauty Sai-gei Kyusei will also be released.And next week, on March 8, Blue Rain by the Theatre Women's Club Beauty Sai-Gei Yusuke will also be released.
Please check it out.
And on March 18, Hello! Project 2023 Spring City Circuit will start.
Beyonds Concert Tour NeoBio will be the first day on March 19.
And on April 1 and 2, we will be at Makuhari Messe for the Hina Fest and
A new event advocated by the Satosanzanoumi
Think Carbon Neutral 2023 will be held at Makuhari Messe.
What can we do?
The Satoyama-Yasakai Movement will be thinking about carbon neutrality and our lives.
Hello! Project members will appear more and more on this channel.
New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel.
We are still in the midst of a difficult time, but let's get through it together.
This time we are joined by Rika Shimakura of Beyonds Subway and
Beyonds Rain Forest, and Minami Okamura from Kawabume.
Good bye.
Please subscribe to our channel.